{
    "subject": "resource/Under_the_Domim_Tree",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "Gila Almagor",
    "human_readable": "Gila Almagor stars in 'Under the Domim Tree'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7293378710746765,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Under the Domim Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7032554149627686,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Gila Almagor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6887773275375366,
            "question": "Who are some other actors in 'Under the Domim Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6421840190887451,
            "question": "Is Gila Almagor an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6219288110733032,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Gila Almagor."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6145601868629456,
            "question": "Are there any other films starring Gila Almagor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5778976082801819,
            "question": "What is Gila Almagor known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47147873044013977,
            "question": "Where was 'Under the Domim Tree' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42129260301589966,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Under the Domim Tree'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3299051523208618,
            "question": "What kind of story does 'Under the Domim Tree' tell?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gila Almagor stars in 'Under the Domim Tree'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7461_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film 'Under the Domim Tree'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7461_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was 'Under the Domim Tree' filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7461_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Gila Almagor known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7461_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7461_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the triple \"Gila Almagor stars in 'Under the Domim Tree'\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Gila Almagor and the movie \"Under the Domim Tree\" together, indicating that she stars in it."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Gila Almagor stars in 'Under the Domim Tree'.\" Specifically, the document with path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7461/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt` states that Under the Domim Tree is based on Gila Almagor\u2019s autobiographical book and that she co-produced it. Additionally, another document mentions that the film won a National Jewish Book Award in 1995, further supporting her involvement as both an author and producer of the work adapted into the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}